- Hello.
- Hello
hello
To those who leave work
Are you not going to work?
You know I worked hard all night
Click Upload
You left it just right
Just click on that manager bastard
Tell them it's okay
Tell the conductor that the bastard is having breakfast.
Well, was the article posted?
yes
Deputy Manager, Engineer Dahye Ah
Upload completed
I quit drinking because of you
Yes, thanks for starting
Very good morning, Seo Ji-woo
Oh, oh, it's hot, Icy
Actress Ah Da-hye
Suspicion of affair arose
The opponent is Group A, a leading business company.
The news is that he is the second son.
Yes, the problem is Ah Ah-hye’s
It's a drug use charge.
I will faithfully participate in the investigation.
At the scene where Mr. Ahn administered drugs...
- Cho Jin-eon, the second son of Seochang Group...
- Cho Jin-eon also...
- It was revealed that he was present several times.
- Get out of here, put this away quickly.
The prosecution began an investigation
- Accordingly, Mr. Cho’s wife…
- Even to Seo Ji-woo...
Seo Ji-woo's husband, Cho Jin-eon...
- Seo Ji-woo, the second daughter of Jarim Apparel...
- Seo Ji-woo...
- Moreover, Seo Ji-woo is Ja-rim’s second daughter.
- Seo Ji-woo's
A fatal disaster for married life...
Jarim Apparel’s owner risk
The risk of being directly connected increases...
- Jarim Apparel to Seo Ji-woo...
- Seo Ji-woo...
The public's attention is focused
It's like this, you know?
I wonder what kind of person's life is like that
No, why is he quiet?
Are you saying you can't live?
No, even if you get married, definitely!
With that bastard, ugh, Mr.
I am there
I was mean to my manager.
This is an article from the Ministry of Social Affairs
How can you be an article in the entertainment department?
Anyway, that bastard craftsman company
I'm going to Jarim Apparel.
Where do you see this?
You're an article in the entertainment department, aren't you, sister?
don't you know that?
Hey, a popular actress
It will have a big impact if you put it on the line and go out.
You say that because you’re upset.
Doesn't a sane person know that?
I know why you ask, then
You just want to be comforted, right?
'I did my best'
‘The thing that ruined Jiwoo’s life was
'It's not my will'
I am not a kid who has been inked once or twice.
A strong child
Lee Kyung-do without a pulpit
I've been pouring alcohol since morning
Sister, when I was 30 years old
You know I quit drinking, right?
why are you like this
Are you only asking Seyoung?
Then why did we call you?
Nigga, yeah, nigga
Hey, Seyoung is among us.
Discernment is the best
Man, you bastard…
- I am discerning between right and wrong...
- child
You guys shut up
Are you going to drink it?
- Kyung-do, are you scared?
- I'm scared
- Should I call you?
- No
Oh, don't do it, sister.
And if you ever get a call
You know you can never use my number, right?
Why is the timing like this?
Ah, manager, manager
yes
Yes? yes
- I'll go.
- You're going?
- what?
- Are you calling me and leaving?
The company wants me to come in
I went on a business trip and turned the car around.
-Why?
- At the conductor's breakfast
- Was there a report that a soju bottle appeared?
- so?
Even a glass of beer with us
I feel a bit sad because you don’t eat it.
Is there any theory that only soju bottles appeared?
Kid, why are you ordering something you don’t want to drink?
- Oh, by the way.
- Don't ask personal questions.
Go to the sauna
Or something, even a shower room, yes?
Smells like a widower, huh?
- What is this?
- Come to your seat
running on your article
- Enjoy amazing emoji jumping
- Yes
Article by Ah Da-hye
Soju bottle appeared
Did you date Ah Da-hye, senior?
Fish Oil, Nice Catch
I've met many people who can't forget their first love.
The guy who has been struggling for 18 years
I think the conductor is the only one.
Isn't it? Deputy Director Lee Kyung-do?
You make up too many stories.
Ah Ah-hye, I’m not worried.
- I'm not worried about my lover.
- Don't do it, really.
Ah Ah-hye's lover
Because you're worried about your wife
Have you had a bottle of soju since morning?
hmm…
It's humanism
- Bro, did you date Seo Ji-woo?
- Conductor, you bastard, conductor.
Oh, so the conductor
Did you really date Seo Ji-woo?
Did you put this in your mouth?
Should I ask you something today, okay?
You put a gag in your mouth, right?
Write articles with your fingers
go to the sauna
What is that?
Go, go, really, really
Isn’t the intern coming home from work?
I'm going to do it now
So?
uh
Hey, wait an hour or something.
It's just a school everywhere
Oh, I don't know
Call me when you're done, then
Yeah
What is it? Where did you go?
uh? what?
What are you doing?
- The 500 won bill is gone.
- Come quickly, just come.
No, banana milk
I have to buy it and eat it.
By any chance, did the 500 won bill disappear?
Ugh
- Huh?
- Come quickly!
Whew…
IC
- Take a look
- All students of Joowon
Come to the comedy club!
there
- Me?
- Have you decided on a club?
club… I won't do it
Okay
Why don't you come and sit down for work?
ah… It’s a theater club, right?
- When you hear the history of geographical disintegration...
- I don't really like that play.
- Oh… Actually, me too
- Good luck!
Uh, huh? Why not?
yes?
Can you sit here for 5 minutes?
Me?
It's because I want to poop
It's a bit troublesome if I'm away.
wait a minute, stay
Uh… that… It's a little...
Ayu, pear, fish oil, pear
Fish oil, pear, pear, fish oil, pear
Huh? if i cum
You're not free either, you know?
No, but I
A student just passing by...
Membership application form, give it to anyone who comes.
- Uh, thanks.
- Oh, that…
Ugh, it was almost like rice.
That… If you are a theater club
Do you also do theater performances?
no way… freshman?
Where do you find yourself asking?
Would you like a mirror?
- Let's write
- yes?
You said look in the mirror?
I said it was presbyopia
I didn't say you were ugly
Perfect to be the main character
Very fun to talk to
You have style.
Is your name Lee Kyung-do?
What about latitude and longitude?
oh… New department? Are you going to become a PD?
No, but what, are you a senior here?
-Why did I say it earlier...
- Fish oil
- I caught one.
- Is it beauty after all?
Even if I sit there for two days, it's okay.
Beauty? Who?
What are you doing in the first meeting?
You said it in the first meeting.
Are you out of your mind?
Hey, same freshmen
Why are you raising the decibel?
freshman?
what? Have I ever said I was a senior?
-No.
- But why are you jumping around like crazy?
Then I'll leave
Now, I need to write down my contact information.
- He, grab him first.
- Uh oh
yes?
-Okay?
- No, no.
- Email, email
- Yes? email?
- email…
- Yes
- Okay, okay? yes
- Oh, yes! Cheer up! I'll contact you!
Supplementary classes?
Ah, what was wrong with the class?
Listen hard?
Oh, I don't know, I'll just go.
See you in Apgujeong, then.
Hey, new student!
Hey, but your school is fun
Hey, hang it up first.
Hey, don't talk nonsense
If that's the case, I should apologize.
Honestly, it's presbyopia
You must have heard it a lot
It's my first time in my life
What kind of evaluation are you?
As you see, as you feel
I just expressed it
You're so angry, you
You live in this world too self-centered.
Do you really think so?
Are you laughing?
Oh, I'm bored. Do you want to go for a drink?
kid, what
Is there no concept in life?
So, while having a drink
Am I clueless?
Let's find out if you have presbyopia
Hey, it's broad daylight now.
I have to go to class
Living this kindly life?
What students study at school
It's not nice, it's natural.
Baby, baby, it's done
Latitude, longitude, longitude?
Let's make a globe together
Hey, what is your name?
What is your name?
Well, I'll toast my first drink and show my ID.
Are you really weak from alcohol?
Hey, wow, that's really funny.
Hey, if you line up empty bottles
I can even build your house
- Show me, show me?
- My house is in Busan.
Hometown?
It's a lie, you idiot.
Come on, I'll line you up.
IC
건배
I'm Jiwoo, Seo Jiwoo
What is it?
Cheers
Department of English Literature, hey, but did you get your third degree?
Do you think I should call you oppa?
This is the face of 1st grade
And what kind of university is this?
Three times?
Aissi, she was just like my mom.
It's so fucking annoying
Drink beolju
Are you overwhelmed?
I adjust it to you like a child.
sweet
boss
Please give me another bottle of soju.
very sweet
Huh? ah…
It's no use
The school bus was cut off.
Oh, my teacher can’t go to the bastard’s house either.
Shall I sleep with you?
Are you excited?
See you again
Ha, really, ah…
Icy, you're like a fool, really.
- Mister, hi.
- Oh my.
Drink less
Do you notice it?
I'm drunk on the smell of your alcohol
If you don't blow, you'll get caught drinking.
What about tea?
Oh, my friend took it.
Oh, by the way, what's happening here all of a sudden?
ah… Oh, you know Hayoung, right?
Oh, that friend you met in America?
Uh, that friend, he goes here.
It's been a while since I came to see you...
Ah, I enjoy this school
Should I go here too?
What about American schools?
Oh, I don't know, I'm going to sleep.
Newbie, hey
Ah, ah, ah, that…
Wow, thank you
- Let's go
- Huh? Where?
- Are you sleeping alone?
- No
- Are you going to take a taxi?
Then drink more!
let's go! let's go!
Let's go together, let's go, let's go together
Huh? uh…
Let’s go home, Wooshik.
Leave me alone
Why do we sleep in the club room?
Then do you let Kyung sleep alone? Were you reassured?
- Is that presbyopia?
-There is no answer, you too.
So stay with us
why? Who says you have presbyopia?
female?
no…
Are you interested in me?
- I heard you said you looked old?
- Yes
To a girl you're interested in
‘Wow, your face looks old’
Can you do it?
no
Are you excited?
kid…
Hey, where are you going?
No, senior, where are you going?
Did you hang out?
Go away
- Let's go
- Go…
Hey, where are you going?
Class should start now
So I should leave now
Where are you going now?
Why are you doing this to me?
I said I'd see you again
It's too one-sided
What are you?
-Where did you sleep last night?
- Director Nam
-Are we strangers?
- Then what is it?
It's obvious that we sleep together
Huh?
No, no, no.
Did you turn around?
It seems like real money
You look handsome
Huh?
- If you keep acting fussy, I'll get scolded.
- You're so fucking cute.
Oh, you can’t say anything without swearing?
Where did you sleep?
I slept in the club room.
Because of you and complete strangers
Are you in disarray?
I should join too
Don't come, you'll definitely leave.
What period is it today?
Hey, why are you curious about that?
Stop paying attention
- Let's have a drink.
- Alcohol?
Hey, all I see is green
I feel like throwing up, because of you
See you later
Five o'clock after class? six hours?
Anyway, let’s meet in the club room.
Go away
- Don't fold it up.
- Don’t mess up…
really… Hey, I...
Uh, oops, sorry.
Ha, I ordered two, Mr.
Now, today, through the media
And when viewed as a technological ecology,
How to our consciousness
About whether it affects
I've talked about it
Until next time, Chapter 3
About authoritarian media theory
Please read all of them
yes
Ah!
It's over, kid.
Eat some candy and go home
Thank you for your hard work
Huh? You work hard
If this happens, it’s a burden on us.
Ah, it's hard to take that off when you're drunk
Shall we have a drink?
- uh? no
- Then why did you come?
uh… I'm trying to stick it out
Ah, sir, is this too much of a burden?
What if your name was Wido?
Hardness is better
Huh? Nothing special happened, so why did you come?
Do you interfere with other people's smoking?
I'm fine, smoke comfortably.
Is this a comfortable atmosphere?
How about swallowing your pretentious cough?
that… He, me, the other seniors…
- I guess the three of us will be enough?
- yes?
The club room was defended again this year.
We also have a new student.
There is no law for people to die
Right?
Freshman, just in time to get out of the room
-Who caught you?
- huh…
Uh, so if I leave
Is there a club extinction crisis or something?
Don't ask me things that make me feel sick
Hey, were you posting a great work?
Hey, on the application right now.
Let's stamp it now
Take a picture, take a picture, take a picture!
- You were good at acting earlier, right?
- uh!
uh
What is Jiwoo doing?
These days?
Uh, I was meeting a friend...
I'm afraid you'll be like this in New York
I told you to just stay
To waste time like this
Are you in?
If you're going to do it yourself, do it properly.
hang up
What are you doing here?
What are you doing? It's dark.
I'm listening to music
Aren't you going home?
I'm going
wake up
go first
Why are you acting so strong?
Are you sorry for not being able to keep your promise?
Did you wait for me?
Did you turn? Are you waiting?
But how do you know I didn’t come?
uh… There is a club meeting
Uh, there's no choice there.
There was, is it okay?
what?
Would you like to hear it? what i like
- Okay, if you're not going, I'll go first.
- Yeah.
Oh no
It's dark in here, just a little while
The last train stopped so there are no people.
- So?
- Wake up, it's dangerous.
Are you taking care of me?
Do you lack affection?
Why do you attach this significance to it?
No, I…
He, I, he…
Am I good at acting?
I’m perfect for the theater club, right?
ah…
Oh, come to your senses.
Oh, wake up quickly, the car is cut off.
Am I good at swearing?
Are you bragging?
Don't you see three?
It seems like it's not enough
I practiced to show off.
You're so unlucky, you
I can only do so much, Chi
No, do you want to show off?
Yeah
What are you doing because you look pretty?
- You confessed, did you?
- what?
You just confessed to me that you wanted to date me.
Me, me?
how?
I told you it was pretty
To be exact, I said she was pretty.
I didn't say it was pretty
It was an encouragement not to swear.
If you say something like that without even thinking about it,
Huh? Are you an asshole?
Let's go together
Oh, if the car is cut off
I'll be homeless for two days
Oh, come quickly
I don't have time to text
yes, yes
- Let's run
- Huh?
What song did you listen to earlier?
A tiring day goes by
two people under the moonlight
one shadow
When I close my eyes
A vague happiness that feels like it can be caught
It's still there
A wounded heart
Even if your dreams cast a shadow
remember me
A person who loves so much that it hurts
That you are by my side
sometimes this way
Even if it seems far away
Even if tears flow from my sad heart
everything happens
Until it becomes a memory
The two of us...
- Take the subway?
- you?
I'm back on the bus
go
uh
- Do you have a cell phone?
- why?
That cell phone...
give me your number
Give me your cell phone
You're not presbyopic, you're young-faced
AC
Uh, sister
- Uh, Gyeongdo, where are you?
- Uh, I'm home.
Um… What are you doing?
It's just there
Okay, I need to get some rest.
Did you get in okay?
Right, yeah, you know, that…
- Jiwoo wants to talk to you.
- Ah... Ah, ah, no!
아니, 걔는 나랑 무슨 얘기를 해
It's not even an article I published.
Oh, my face is also blurry.
What does this have to do with me?
That's right, kid, what you say is very true...
Hey, I knew it would be like this
It should have been handed over to the Ministry of Social Affairs.
This, shit…
Anyway, sister, I don’t think that’s the case.
Sister, even if you think so, right? uh
Uh, I'm sorry. Please take care of me.
Uh, uh
Hey, it's not me
What am I guilty of?
Not me, no! Tsk, Mr…
Yes, this is the entertainment department of Dongwoon Ilbo.
Ah, yes
This is not our department
Well, maybe something.
Isn’t it from the social department?
Yes, I will connect you with the department in charge.
Deputy Director, when did you date Seo Ji-woo?
Oh, what if they come to visit me?
- How many years will we see each other again?
- Hey, Mr. Lee.
No, even when the deputy chief new reporter
There was a report that he came once.
Hey, yeah
Yes, this is the entertainment department of Dongwoon Ilbo.
Yes, Lee Kyung-do?
uh… What are you looking for...
Ah, an acquaintance…
You are not there
- Yes, say you went on a business trip, business trip, business trip.
- Oh, you went on a business trip.
I'll tell you when you come, the name...
ah… hmm…
Ugh, Mr…
- It was a woman.
- Will you shut up?
Exactly Seo Ji-woo’s age group.
A voice?
Will you go back?
- Okay.
- IC
Oh my, I'm annoyed
- This is a concert?
- That's right, book concert.
- ah…
- uh?
It's not too late, let's go out now
Uh, it's started, it's started
When Chusa was seven years old
Ipchuncheop called Ipchundae-gil
I wrote it in front of the front door.
Beonam Chae Je-gong happened to be passing by.
Looking at Chusa’s handwriting
‘He is a world-famous penman.’
From a young age like this
Chusa has extraordinary talent.
It is very famous for its typeface.
Chusa left behind many poems.
Oh, maybe two of them
‘I am Chusa Kim Jeong-hee’
‘I know how to write a poem’, Son
- Huh? yes
- 'When running away'
Chusa's 'Escape', Bravo!
- Come out.
- Are you going out?
- Come out, I need to give you a cultural gift certificate.
- Oh, yeah.
‘Runaway Poetry’, I also read that poem
I really like it
I proposed with that poem.
thank you
Do you like books?
no
You seem like a Korean literature student.
Haha, I just like Chusa.
Ah… That poem earlier?
- Is it ‘on the run’?
- Yes
- Do you memorize it?
- Uh
- Try it.
- Huh?
- Here?
- Yes
You're curious, the title is a gag.
What is ‘running away’?
I did that too, but the title was funny.
But that ‘run away’
It wasn't like running away.
Chusa loved his wife very much.
But my wife died first.
The vision I created at that time, that was
Um…
ah…
Who appealed to Old Man Wolha?
In the afterlife, couples are born interchangeably.
A thousand miles away I die
you are alive
This sad heart of mine
I wish you knew too
Huh?
Ooh, are you crying?
Uh, why…
Oh, it's so sad
Huh?
Hey, how much I miss you
Should I write a poem like that?
That's right
Hey, but, you just do that
I guess he's a fool
Mr. Lee
Child…
Oh, I'm annoyed
Ah…
Why are you laughing so scary?
- Just cry or eat me.
-Are you clueless?
- It's really consistent.
- What?
Do you want to wear our company brand?
Eat well and live well
I sold it, why?
Even if I don’t sell you too
eat well and live well
yes
That… What is that article...
disappeared 10 years ago
It just showed up...
What you want to say is about the article?
I know you haven't been having a good time.
How is your health?
It's still the same, I'm living on psychiatric drugs
It's still the same thing that makes me shut my mouth
- Is it delicious?
- Will you eat it because it’s delicious?
Don't drink it because it's awkward
Aren’t you drinking it because you’re nervous?
why don't you drink beer
Jiwooya
- Just say what you have to say.
- Are you sure?
-Do you want to say something?
- Uh, do it.
Godot won’t come even if I wait
They say hardness is coming?
If I wait, will you come?
I've waited too
We are members of society now, right?
A 20-year-old play, That Damn Thing
What are you dragging me here for?
That damn play?
You little bastard
The play's title is
- Is it ‘Waiting for Godot’?
- Yes
Do you like theater?
I'm not sure yet
But why did you join the theater club?
I feel sorry for you so I can't pass by.
너 팔 열라 후들거려
Hey, hey
Huh? uh? You're a poop sister, right?
poop? where do you go again
Did you hit a poop accident?
Ohaha, do you just poop in the toilet?
No, but then
My sister says her stomach hurts
If I cum there, I will be free too.
You said you couldn't do it and just ran away.
Um, it's poop, it's poop
Shit, shit, you really are shit
- Just go around pooping...
- Hey
Just stay still, maybe Lee Kyung-do
The person who signed up...
Yes, I am
Hey, Lee Kyung-do, you and this guy
After fighting like that, you're dating?
- Yes
- The club room does not appear.
You're only dating, what's the script?
Did you memorize everything?
- Are you performing? hero?
- kid…
It's not the face of a main character.
- Okay, let's go quickly, let's cool down.
- Why is my drink cold?
- Are you going for a drink?
- Yes
- Oh, no.
-Why not?
- Shall we go together?
- His eyes went crazy.
Why do you like it so much?
no!
- Ta-da!
- salty
- It’s longitude.
- That way.
Longitude!
yes?
I told you to speak up, Jondae?
That's all pretense
Another pretense
Hey, you are the most pretentious.
Sister, what department are you in?
Western studies, but it’s all pretense.
Art? Damn, fuck you all.
Close your ears, this is just swearing
Sister, sister, I'm swearing at you
Please teach me too
Kyungdo, break up.
I have a good heart
Did you see it? Fish oil, hey
Have you ever opened your heart?
Even if you can't see it, you can see it
Open this bastard too, it’s a pretense.
No, I can't see it but I can see it
I mean, is it poop?
Look, your life is shit.
Oh, really! I…
If you're shit, you're screwed.
- I'm really...
- Wow, really again...
- Shouldn't I go? let's go
- Umm, kid, it's okay, it's okay.
Huh? Where are you going? This is just the beginning.
I feel like I have to go
Oh, seniors aren’t going home?
This is everyone’s room
Ah, I want to sleep alone, I want to sleep alone too.
Oh no, no, no, no
It goes like this, huh?
What am I, you bastard?
No, sorry, my neck hurts.
No, no! Come down, come down!
don't do it! Hey, don't do that
You guys stop fighting
please
- Oh, just stop it.
- Yes
Did you say you were taking a leave of absence for this?
As soon as you enroll?
mom, i go to school
I want to stop going around
Jiwoo, stop!
Nothing entered my head
I have no interest in Western art history.
Are you doing it because you like it, studying?
Gotta have a degree, whatever, a degree
So I just want to go to college here
I'll prepare for the college entrance exam, okay?
Why can't you live your life proudly?
What is lacking?
I do everything you ask me to do.
Is it depression or something?
Why are you living on medication? Really...
uh? Why like this
Life is shabby, are you?
Let's live in a good mood
Please, Jiwoo?
Ah, cell phone
What's wrong? what's the matter?
Am I pathetic?
Coming at this time without any plan...
Pathetic, isn’t it? It's hardness
What is so pathetic
I miss you
I'm so glad you came running like this
i like you
Jiwoo, I
Do you know why I joined the theater club?
you…
I'm sitting on the club bench
Actually, what is the club doing?
I went in without knowing.
Because of you
I'm going to England
Thanks to you, I'm free now
thank you for the article
Just hit me?
You really don’t trust people
Then and now
Thank you
Thanks to your article, I got divorced.
Thank you to the point of tears
It's all my fault
Kneel from the beginning
Even though I went in, it was a little…
What, what are you talking about again?
What about my marriage? M&A?
But our side was at a disadvantage.
Did I spend my youth a bit noisily?
I am grateful just for accepting it.
Something like that
Depression that I live with
Panic disorder is also my fault
Infertility is definitely my fault
Oh, I'm infertile
Are you saying there was a rumor going around?
Well, it's not like we're in love.
That bastard is cheating
It's not even a shock
Still...
Miserable?
아, 너무 대놓고 그러니까
취하면 가끔
쌍욕 좀 듣고
아이, 씨발, 개새끼, 그거 씨
그러지 마
마음이 노골노골 그런다고
정 붙어, 그러지 마
Are you out of your mind?
Even in this situation
Are you going to blurt it out like that?
It doesn't seem to count at all
I have been persistently filing for divorce.
Thanks to you, I really finished it this time.
Thank you so much, truly.
Yeah, that's a good thing, that's it.
- I'm going
- sit down
What? Is there anything else you want to say?
I don't know if this will be a scoop or not
- I'm going to give you one as repayment of your favor.
- No, that's enough.
Oh, why are you being so disgusting?
Why are you so damned!
You wrote my divorce article
I'll give it to you alone
Because I want to look cool
Divorce proceedings have been underway for a long time.
Be sure to put it in
Wow…
Jiwooya
While I was confirming your husband’s article,
I had a hard time sleeping at night
Were you worried?
Sit facing each other like this
I wonder if I'm just listening to bullshit
- Bullshit?
- Yeah, bullshit.
Crazy bullshit, you cruel bastard!
See you at the funeral
Either you die or I die
Guys, let's talk about Confucianism.
Is there anyone who can't come out? hand
Why don't you raise your hand?
That's right, the good-looking guy always comes out.
Now, who else can't come out?
Ah, what else…
Gyeongdo, this Saturday at 3 o'clock
Ah…
I can't go
Do you want to quit school life?
What is this handsome bastard?
I can't because I'm presbyopic.
Shinbang and image damage
I’m so presbyopic, I’m sorry.
Hey, if you have presbyopia… Longitude!
- Sister, no, this is
- good conversation
- I don't do it.
- Don't do it, don't do it.
- A hopeful conclusion!
- let's do it
- Mr. Kyung-do’s identity was stolen.
- Ah, ah, fish oil, Seo Ji-woo!
The conductor's bastard is in other media.
Please make it a news story...
This frustrating situation
What do you think?
I was young, immature and delicate.
Ah…
It was pure and sincere.
18 years of friendship, so
Don't push yourself towards romance?
You got caught up in me for no reason
Life almost got messed up again
Wrong, wrong in two places.
I've never been involved
I've never been twisted